// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: " Which of these components are used in a Java program for compilation, debugging, and execution?",
  answer: "JDK",
  options: [
    "JDK",
    "JRE",
    "ClassLoader",
    "Debugger"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "Which of these literals can be contained in a float data type variable?",
  answer: "-3.4e+038",
  options: [
    "-3.4e+038",
    "+1.7e+308",
    "-3.4e+038",
    "-1.7e+308"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: " What is BigDecimal.ONE?",
  answer: "it is a static variable that has a value of 1 on a scale of 0",
  options: [
    "it is a custom-defined statement",
    "it is a wrong statement",
    "it is a static variable that has a value of 1 on a scale of 0",
    "it is a static variable that has a value of 1 on a scale of 10"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: " When an expression consists of int, double, long, float, then the entire expression will get promoted into a data type that is:",
  answer: "double",
  options: [
    "float",
   "double",
  "int",
    "long"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "Which of the following operators can operate on a boolean variable?",
  answer: "A,B and C",
  options: [
    "&&","==","?:","+="
  ]
},
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: " Out of these statements, which ones are incorrect?",
    answer: "The division operator / has comparatively higher precedence as compared to a multiplication operator",
    options: [
     "The Brackets () have the highest precedence","The equal to = operator has the lowest precedence",
      "The addition operator + and the subtraction operator â€“ have an equal precedence","The division operator / has comparatively higher precedence as compared to a multiplication operator"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "java supports what type of inheritence?",
    answer: "Single Inheritence",
    options: [
    "Single Inheritence",
    "Multiple Inheritence",
    "Multilevel Inheritence",
    "Hybrid Inheritence"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is it called when the child object also gets killed when the parent object is killed in the program?",
    answer: "Composition",
    options: [
    "Encapsulation","Association","Aggregation","Composition"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 9,
    question: " How does one identify if a compilation unit is an interface or class from a .class file?",
    answer: "Java source file header",
    options: [
    "Extension of the compilation unit","Java source file header","The class and interface cannot be differentiated","The unit type must be used to postfix interface or class name"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 10,
    question: " Out of these methods of the String class, which one can be used for testing the strings for equality?",
    answer: "equals()",
    options: [
     "isequals()","isequal()","equals()","equal()"
    ]
  }
];
